<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title><![CDATA[Matthew]]></title>
  
  <link href="/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://yoursite.com/"/>
  <updated>2017-05-06T14:38:09.000Z</updated>
  <id>http://yoursite.com/</id>
  
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Matthew]]></name>
    
  </author>
  
  <generator uri="http://hexo.io/">Hexo</generator>
  
  <entry>
    <title><![CDATA[PSO Algorithm]]></title>
    <link href="http://yoursite.com/2017/05/06/PSO%20Algorithm/"/>
    <id>http://yoursite.com/2017/05/06/PSO Algorithm/</id>
    <published>2017-05-06T14:38:09.000Z</published>
    <updated>2017-05-06T14:38:09.000Z</updated>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[PSO AlgorithmQuote The PSO algorithm is an evolutionary computation, which is propsoed by Dr.Eberhart and Dr.Kennedy. This algorithm is originally based on the study of bird predation behaviour, inspired by the rules of birds cluster and then build a simplified model by using swarm intelligence. And now, PSO algorithm is based on the observation of animal cluster activity, making use of the information sharing among the individuals in the group which makes the motion of the whole group evolve from disorder to order in the problem solving space, so that you can get theoptimum solution. Algorithm Inrtoduction As mentioned earlier, PSO simulated predation behavior of birds. Imagine a scenario: a flock of birds in the random search of food. There is only one piece of food in this area. All the birds don’t know where the food is. But they know how far away the food is. So what is the best strategy to find food?. The simplest and most effective way is to search the area around the nearest bird. PSO is used to solve the optimization problem. In PSO, the solution of each optimization problem is a bird in the search space. We call it a particle. All particles have an adaptive value determined by the optimized function, and each particle has a velocity that determines the direction and distance of their flight. Then the particles follow the optimal particle in the solution space. PSO is initialized to a group of random particles. And then find the optimal solution by iteration. In each iteration, the particle updates itself by tracking two “extremes”. The first one is the optimal solution of the particle itself, which is called the pBest. The other extreme is the optimal solution which is found in the whole population. The extreme value is the global extreme value gBest. In addition, it is possible to use only a part of the neighborhood as a particle without the whole population. When finding these two optimal values, the particle updates its speed and new position according to the following formula: $V=\omega *V+C1*rand()*(pbest-present)+C2*rand()*(gbest-present)$ $present=present+V$ In the formulas above, V is the particle velocity. C1 and C2 are learning factors. \omega is a weighting factor. The rand() is random number between zero and one. Parameter Setting The number of particle generally take 20 to 40. In fact, 10 particles can get good results. Particle length: This is determined by the optimization problem, is the length of the problem solution. The scope of the particle: by the optimization problem, each dimension can be set different range. The learning factors usually take 2, also depending on the specific situation. Break condition: Maximum number of cycles and minimum error requirements. Matlab CodeYou can get code here.]]></content>
    <summary type="html">
    <![CDATA[PSO Algorithm]]>
    </summary>
    
      <category term="Matlab" scheme="http://yoursite.com/tags/Matlab/"/>
    
      <category term="May 2017" scheme="http://yoursite.com/categories/May-2017/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title><![CDATA[Markdown(III)]]></title>
    <link href="http://yoursite.com/2017/05/05/Markdown(III)/"/>
    <id>http://yoursite.com/2017/05/05/Markdown(III)/</id>
    <published>2017-05-05T04:55:09.000Z</published>
    <updated>2017-05-05T05:46:08.000Z</updated>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[Something about Markdown(III) II. The grammar of MarkdownTableThe grammar of tables is a little bit complex. You can clearly see how does it work below. Code BoxIf you are a programmar, the code box which you want to put into you personal website is really important. The picture below clearly show it. The Cut-Off LineThe cut-off line just needs “*“. III. The feel of MarkdownThe grammar of Markdown is not only these, there is more interesting thing for you to explore. In my opinion, the Markdown is an amazing language and helps me a lot especially in building my own website. I will practice more so that I can have a better command of Markdown and make much progress.]]></content>
    <summary type="html">
    <![CDATA[S]]>
    </summary>
    
      <category term="Markdown" scheme="http://yoursite.com/tags/Markdown/"/>
    
      <category term="May 2017" scheme="http://yoursite.com/categories/May-2017/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title><![CDATA[Markdown(II)]]></title>
    <link href="http://yoursite.com/2017/05/02/Markdown(II)/"/>
    <id>http://yoursite.com/2017/05/02/Markdown(II)/</id>
    <published>2017-05-02T14:20:49.000Z</published>
    <updated>2017-05-05T05:19:04.000Z</updated>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[Something about Markdown(II) II. The grammar of MarkdownTitleThere are six level heading in Markdown, and every heading needs one space before the title. The picture above clearly show the grammar of the title. ListIn Markdown, the display of list just needs “-“ or “*”, which is formed of unordered list. As for the ordered list, you just need add “1.”, “2.”,and “3.” before words. The picture under the passage clearly show it. QuoteIf you want yo quote something to your essay, you just need to insert “&gt;” before the word. Picture and LinkThe grammar of inserting picture and link is similar. The difference between them is “!”.By the way, I use this website to store my pictures. Bold and ItalicThe grammar of bold and italic is simple. The picture under the passage clearly show it.]]></content>
    <summary type="html">
    <![CDATA[Some]]>
    </summary>
    
      <category term="Markdown" scheme="http://yoursite.com/tags/Markdown/"/>
    
      <category term="May 2017" scheme="http://yoursite.com/categories/May-2017/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title><![CDATA[Markdown(I)]]></title>
    <link href="http://yoursite.com/2017/05/01/Markdown(I)/"/>
    <id>http://yoursite.com/2017/05/01/Markdown(I)/</id>
    <published>2017-05-01T05:49:57.000Z</published>
    <updated>2017-05-05T05:17:03.000Z</updated>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[Something about Markdown(I) Introduction Markdown is a light weight language, which has many merits. If you want to learn about more details, please click here.I will briefly introuduce the grammar of this language and my feel. I.About Markdown We can learn from the introduction that the Markdown is a light weight language. This language focuses on the simple grammar instead of the complex composing, which makes us concentrate on writting itself rather than optimizing the structure. What’s more, many editors and websites support this language, such as sublime ,jianshu and so on. Last but not least, when you finish the task with Markdown, the format of exportation could be varied. The official document of Markdown You can refer to more information with the below websites. http://markdown-here.com/ http://daringfireball.net/projects/markdown/syntax http://wowubuntu.com/markdown/#list The merits of Markdown Focus on your content instead of composing. Easily export files with the format of HTML, PDF and md. Have a simple grammar and easy to learn. The tool of MarkdownI strongly suggest Mou and Macdown, if you are using the Mac. And also, MarkdownPad and MarkPad are very suuitable for Windows.]]></content>
    <summary type="html">
    <![CDATA[Somethi]]>
    </summary>
    
      <category term="Markdown" scheme="http://yoursite.com/tags/Markdown/"/>
    
      <category term="May 2017" scheme="http://yoursite.com/categories/May-2017/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title><![CDATA[Preface]]></title>
    <link href="http://yoursite.com/2017/04/27/Preface/"/>
    <id>http://yoursite.com/2017/04/27/Preface/</id>
    <published>2017-04-27T14:52:06.000Z</published>
    <updated>2017-05-03T14:20:09.000Z</updated>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[First of all, I am very grateful for the help of Dropar, who is my roommate and give me lots of helpful suggestions for my website. And of course, the process of building my website is very hard. I have spent almost a week building mt website. If anyone has some trouble, you can contact me with my Wechat ID: Wangbin-matthew. Finally, make a brief introuduction of my website. My website records some of my experiences and what I am learning now. If website has some mistakes, please contact me immediately. And also I am very happy to communicate with each other and make progress togehter.]]></content>
    <summary type="html">
    <![CDATA[]]>
    </summary>
    
      <category term="Preface" scheme="http://yoursite.com/tags/Preface/"/>
    
      <category term="May 2017" scheme="http://yoursite.com/categories/May-2017/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title><![CDATA[Hello World]]></title>
    <link href="http://yoursite.com/2017/04/27/hello-world/"/>
    <id>http://yoursite.com/2017/04/27/hello-world/</id>
    <published>2017-04-27T13:37:02.000Z</published>
    <updated>2017-05-05T17:09:53.000Z</updated>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[Hello World!Hello my website!]]></content>
    <summary type="html">
    <![CDATA[Hello World!Hello my website!]]>
    </summary>
    
  </entry>
  
</feed>
